{"quiz": {"questions": [{"Hint": null, "question": "Did they fight against the Axis Powers?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 267, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Were they joined by the USSR and USA in 1941?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 266, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Was the Axis Powers Germany, Italy and Japan?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 265, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What did they fight against?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "against the Axis Powers"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "against the Axis Powers"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 264, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What were they joined by in 1941?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "by the USSR and USA"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "by the USSR and USA"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 263, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who fought against the Axis Powers?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 262, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Were the UK and France joined by the USSR and USA in 1941?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 261, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Were the Allied Powers initially led by the UK and France?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 260, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Did the UK and France fight against the Axis Powers?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 259, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who were joined by the USSR and USA in 1941?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 258, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "When were they joined by the USSR and USA?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "in 1941"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "in 1941"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 257, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What was the Axis Powers?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "Germany, Italy and Japan"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "Germany, Italy and Japan"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 256, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who was Germany, Italy and Japan?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "the Axis Powers"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "the Axis Powers"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 255, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "When were the UK and France joined by the USSR and USA?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "in 1941"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "in 1941"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 254, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What did the UK and France fight against?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "against the Axis Powers"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "against the Axis Powers"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 253, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What were the Allied Powers initially led by?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "by the UK and France"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "by the UK and France"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 252, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What were initially led by the UK and France?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "the Allied Powers"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "the Allied Powers"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 251, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What were the UK and France joined by in 1941?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "by the USSR and USA"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "by the USSR and USA"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 250, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What fought against the Axis Powers?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "the UK and France"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "the UK and France"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 249, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What were joined by the USSR and USA in 1941?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "the UK and France"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "the UK and France"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 248, "skippable": true}]}}